A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Photographs FA738
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Photographs
1948-1996
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA738
50 Cubic Feet 110 document boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Photographic holdings were transferred through multiple Accessions in 2012. Accessions continue as necessary.
Arrangement
Photographs are intellectually arranged into three series:
Series 1: Jobs.
Series 2: Ford Foundation Trustees, Officers and Staff Photographs.
Series 3: General, Program, and Project Photographs.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains Jobs photos, as well as photographs of Ford Foundation trustees, officers, staff, and photographs of Foundation projects, programs and activities.
Photographs
- Jobs, 1
  - 1 - Ford Foundation Field Office, New Delhi, India, 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Photographer: Kleinberg, Ernest
    India
  - 2 - Nilokheri Training Center: Graduation: India, 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 3 - Allahabad Agricultural Institute: Village Worker Couple, 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 3, 4)
  - 4 - Ramakrishna Agricultural Institute, 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 5 - T.C.A. Extension Workers: Community Development, 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 6 - South India community development and village improvement, 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 7 - Central and North India community development and village improvement, 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 8 - Old and New Delhi, India, 1953 January (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 9 - Ford Foundation Field Office Karachi, Pakistan, 1953 January (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Pakistan
  - 10 - Technical High School for Boys - Karachi, Pakistan, 1953 January (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 11 - Home Economics College for Girls, Pakistan, 1953 January (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 12 - Demonstration of American Plow, Iran (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Photographer: Kleinberg, Ernest. No prints in file, see negatives.
    Iran
  - 13 - Refugee Boy's Story: Berlin, Germany, 1952 December (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Germany
  - 14 - Displaced Persons Camps, Germany, 1952 December (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 15 - Refugee Camps: Berlin, Germany, 1952 December (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 16 - Vocational Training Center: Heilsberg, 1952 December (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 17 - Rehabilitation and Vocational Training Center at Hanover Prison, 1952 December (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 18 - Rehabilitation and Vocational Training: Herzogsaegmuehle, 1952 December (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 19 - Rehabilitation and Vocational Training: Meinwerk, 1952 December (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 20 - Lutheran Boys and Girls Home: Berlin., 1952 December (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 21 - Free University - Berlin, 1952 December (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 22 - Frankfurt University, 1952 December (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 23 - UNHCR Meeting, Switzerland, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Switzerland
  - 24 - Vienna Housing Project, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Austria
  - 25 - Displaced Persons Camps: Austria, 1952 December (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 26 - AFSC Projects: South Italy, 1953 February (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Italy
  - 27 - MCC-AFSC Projects: Rome, 1952 December (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 28 - Displaced Persons Camps: Italy, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 29 - Chekhov Publications: Berlin and Frankfurt, 1952 December (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - 30 - Jury Study on Social Behavior (Box 3, Folder 31)
    United States
  - 31 - Intercultural Publications, Inc., 1952 December (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - 32 - Russian Emigres in United States, Detroit, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Photographer: Clark, J.
  - 33 - International Farm Youth Exchange Program, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Photographer: ACME. No prints in file, see negatives.
    Netherlands
  - 34 - International Farm Youth Exchange Program (File Missing), 1953 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Photographer: ACME. No prints or negatives. File is Missing.
  - 35 - New York University - Sun Stove, 1955 January (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Photographer: Stevens, Roy. No prints in file, see negatives.
  - 36 - National Municipal League, 1952 November (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Photographer: Gillette, G. No prints in file, see negatives.
  - 37 - Education: Harvard University (Box 4, Folder 38)
    No prints in file, see negatives.
  - 38 - Education: Oberlin College (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - 39 - Education: Bay City Schools Project (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - 41 - Education: TFAE - Institute Of Philosophical Research (File Missing) (Box 4, Folder 41)
    No prints or negatives. File is Missing.
  - 42 - Education: Adult Education (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - 43 - Ford Foundation Trustees Meeting, 1952 December (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Photographer: Page, Homer
  - 44 - Ford Foundation Program Committee (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - 45 - Ford Foundation offices, Tuerk House, 2 Oak Knoll Terrace, Pasadena, California, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - 46 - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees, Finance Committee, 1954 November (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Photographer: Stevens, Roy
  - 47 - H. Rowan Gaither and William McPeak with Chart, Ford Foundation Board of Trustees, Increasing Faculty Salaries, 1955 March (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - 47.1 - Advisory Committee on Faculty Salaries (Box 4, Folder 48)
    Photographer: Latham, S. No prints in file, see negatives.
  - 48 - Catholic University of Lille, France, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    Photographer: Latham, S.
    France
  - 49 - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees Meeting, 1955 December (Box 4, Folder 50, 51, Box 132)
    Photographer: Koner, M.
    General
    11x14 prints are housed in Box 132.
  - 50 - Restoration of YMCA, Manila, Philippines (Box 4, Folder 52)
    Philippines
  - 51 - Village Health Educational Program, 1957 June (Box 5, Folder 53)
    Photographer: Galiher, Claudia
  - 52 - Karachi Polytechnic Institute, Pakistan (File Missing) (Box 5, Folder 54)
    No prints or negatives. File is missing.
  - 53 - Karachi Polytechnic Institute, Pakistan (File Missing) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - 54 - College of Home Economics: Karachi, Pakistan (Box 5, Folder 54)
    No prints in file. See negatives.
  - 55 - Village and Small Industries Institute (File Missing) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - 56 - Government and Technical Institute: Inseino (File Missing) (Box 5, Folder 54)
    Burma
  - 57 - Mass Education Council (File Missing) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - 58 - Agricultural Institute: Pyinmana (File Missing) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - 59 - Rangoon Technical High School, Burma, 1957 July (Box 5, Folder 55)
    Photographer: Olsen
  - 60 - Agricultural Institute: Pyinmana, Burma, 1957 January (Box 5, Folder 56)
    Photographer: U Maung Maung Tin
  - 61 - International Institute of Advanced Buddhistic Studies, Burma, 1957 June (Box 5, Folder 57)
    Photographer: Soderland
  - 62 - Agricultural Training School: Sumbawa, Indonesia, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    Photographer: Gillsaeter, S.
    Indonesia
  - 63 - Museum Ratna Wartha: Ubud, Bali. (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - 64 - Balai Pustaka (Governmentt Printing Press), 1957 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - 65 - Ford Foundation Office: Jakarta, Indonesia, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 61, 62)
    Photographer: Harapan Photo
  - 66 - American Political Science Association: Congressional Internship Program (Box 5, Folder 63)
    Photographer: Kerr, J.
  - 67 - National Forensic League: Wyoming, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    Photographer: Gerdts, J.
  - 68 - Austen Riggs Center, Stockbridge, MA, 1956 December (Box 5, Folder 65)
    Photographer: Fried, L.
  - 69 - New York University: International Legal Studies, 1952 December (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - 70 - American Universities Field Staff, 1956 November (Box 5, Folder 67)
    Photographer: Ultang, D.
  - 71 - Institute for Theoretical Physics, 1956 November (Box 5, Folder 68)
    Photographer: Taconis, K.
    Denmark
  - 72 - Personnel Book: "You and the Ford Foundation", 1956 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    Photographer: Glenn, B.
  - 73 - Willy Brandt (Mayor of Berlin) at Ford Foundation offices, 1958 February (Box 6, Folder 70)
    Includes Willy Brandt (Mayor of Berlin), Senator Guenter Klein (of Berlin), Ambassador Broich-Oppert (German representative to United Nations), and Shepard Stone (Ford Foundation officer).
  - 74 - Humanities Committee Conference, 1958 March (Box 6, Folder 71)
    Photographer: Simmons, William
  - 75 - Karachi Polytechnic, Pakistan, 1957 October (Box 6, Folder 72, 73)
  - 76 - Karachi College of Home Economics, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - 77 - Burdwan Farm: near Calcutta, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - 78 - Village Aid Training Center: near Lalamusa, Pakistan (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - 79 - Small Industries Training Center, India, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - 80 - Village Aid Training Center near Lahore, Pakistan, 1957 November (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - 81 - Parsi Boys School: Karachi, Pakistan, 1957 November (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - 82 - Village Aid: Village Scenes: near Lahore, Pakistan, 1957 November (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - 83 - Village Aid Work and Village Scenes, Pakistan, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - 84 - College of Home and Domestic Science, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - 85 - Village Aid Institute and Village Activity, Pakistan, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - 86 - East Pakistan Polytechnic: Dacca, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - 87 - International Farm Youth Exchange, Pakistan, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - 88 - Holy Family Hospital, Dacca, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - 89 - Tejgaon Village Aid Institute, Pakistan, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - 90 - The Nanquagud Vidyapeeth-Mysore Training of Village Workers, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - 91 - Balsahyog Extension Center, India, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - 92 - Law Institute, New Delhi, India, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - 93 - Ford Foundation Field Office, New Delhi, India, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - 94 - University of New Delhi: Chair in American Civilization, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - 95 - Douglas Ensminger Portrait, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    Photographer: Simmons, William. No print in file, see negatives.
  - 96 - Misc. Scenes around East and West Pakistan, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - 97 - Southern Languages Book Trust, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - 98 - Central Institute of Education, Lady Irwin Higher Secondary School, India, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - 99 - Small Industries Mobile Sales Van, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - 100 - Small Industries Program - Calcutta, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - 101 - Small Industries Program - Calcutta, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - 102 - Small Industries Program - Calcutta, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - 103 - Delhi Cloth Mills, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - 104 - Urban Planning: Delhi Municipal Corp., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 102, 103)
  - 105 - Delhi Orientation and Training Centers for Foreign Technicians, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - 106 - Training, small industries, home economics, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    Nepal
  - 107 - Rural and Village Community Development, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - 108 - Village Aid Work Around Gandhigram, India, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - 109 - Small Industries Demonstration Vans, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - 110 - Rural and Village Community Development Block, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - 111 - Nilokheri B.D.O. Training Center, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - 112 - International Farm Youth Exchange, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - 113 - Leather Works Training Centers, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - 114 - Rural Health Institute, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - 115 - Rural Development Program, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    Photographer: Young, L.
  - 116 - TV-Radio Workshop-Omnibus, 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - 117 - International Farm Youth Exchange Program (File Missing), 1955 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    No prints or negatives available. File is missing.
  - 118-119 - Arab Development Society: a) Agricultural Vocational School for Boys; b) Rural Development Program, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    Jordan
  - 120 - Near East Foundation: Village Schools, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    Photographer: Near East Foundation. No prints in file, see negatives.
  - 121 - Hospital Grants Program, 1955 December (Box 9, Folder 119, Box 132)
  - 122 - First Public Sale of Ford Motor Company Stock, 1956 January (Box 10, Folder 120, Box 132)
    Photographer: Eisenstadt, Alfred
  - 122.1 - First Public Sale of Ford Motor Company Stock, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - 123 - East European Fund: Research Program on U.S.S.R., 1953 January (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - 124 - National Manpower Council, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    Photographer: Wide World Photos, Inc.
  - 125 - National Civil Service League, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 124)
  - 126 - Center for Advance Study in Behavioral Sciences (File Missing), 1954 (Box 10, Folder 125)
  - 127 - Trustee Election of John J. McCloy, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 126)
    Photographer: ACME
  - 128 - Trustees Election: D. Brownlee, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 127)
  - 129 - Trustees Election: James Black, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - 130 - Trustee Election of Julius Stratton, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 129, Box 132)
  - 131 - Paul Hoffman Resignation, 1953 February (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - 132 - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees Meeting, Dyke Brown, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - 133 - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees Meeting, William McPeak, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - 134 - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees Meeting, Don Price, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - 135 - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees Meeting, Thomas Carroll, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - 136 - Overseas Representatives: Meeting, 1953 May (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - 137 - H. Rowan Gaither Visit to Gov-Gen of Pakistan, Ghulam Mohammed., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - 138 - Messrs. Henry Heald and H. Rowan Gaither, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 137)
    Photographer: Merrim, L.
  - 139 - Portraits - Ford Foundation Trustees (File Missing), 1953 December (Box 10, Folder 138)
    Photographer: Rosenberg, S. No prints or negatives available. File is missing.
  - 140 - Portraits: Ford Foundation Staff Members (File Missing), 1953 December (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Near East Photo Correspondence, Captions, in references to Jobs 150-159. (Box 10, Folder 140)
    Photographer: Machlin, S.
  - 150 - Musa Bey Alami Boys Plantation: Jericho, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 141, Box 11, Folder 142, 143)
  - 151 - Arab Development Society - Jericho, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - 152 - Spafford Children's Hospital, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - 153 - Beirut Women's College, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 146)
    Lebanon
  - 154 - American Univerity Beirut, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - 155 - American University, Beirut Farm, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - 156 - Khalil Ghatta's Chicken Farm - Talabaya, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - 157 - Agricultural Cooperative: Varamin Plains, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - 158 - Near East Foundation Center And Demonstration Project, Mamazon, 1957 October (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - 159 - Town of Ghez El Dja, Iran, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - 160 - Dr. H.W. Magoun - UCLA, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 153)
  - 161 - Dr. Linus Pauling: California Institute of Technology, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 154)
  - 162 - Dr. Bruno Bettelheim, Sonia Shankman Orthogenic School, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 155)
  - 163 - St. Louis Urban and Regional Studies, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 156, 157)
  - 164 - St. Louis Urban and Regional Studies, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 158)
  - 165 - Foreign Area Training Fellowships, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 159)
  - 166 - Educational Television, St. Louis, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 160)
  - 173 - Mental Health Advisory Group, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 161)
  - 174 - Southern Appalachian Mountain Area, Berea College Study, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 162)
  - 175 - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Program, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 163)
  - 176 - International Press Inst. Conference, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 164)
  - 177 - New York City Opera Company, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 165)
  - 178 - Cleveland Playhouse, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 166)
  - 179 - Indian Steel Training and Educational Program: In Step (Box 13, Folder 167)
  - 180 - Program for the Aging, Ohio, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 168)
  - 181 - Hospital Grants, Ohio, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 169)
  - 182 - Use of Behavioral Sciences, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - 183 - University of Chicago, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - 184 - Northwestern University, 1958 May (Box 13, Folder 172)
  - 185 - National Merit Scholarship, 1958 May (Box 13, Folder 173)
  - 186 - College Teacher Training, Business and Economics, University of Wisconsin, 1958 May (Box 13, Folder 174)
  - 187 - Educational Television, 1958 May (Box 13, Folder 175)
  - 188 - Inter-University Committee for Research on Consumer Behavior, 1958 May (Box 13, Folder 176)
  - 189 - Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1958 May (Box 14, Folder 177)
  - 190 - Hospital Grants, 1958 May (Box 14, Folder 178)
  - 191 - Polish Exchange Program: Princeton University, New Jersey, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 179)
  - 192 - Polish Exchange Program: Princeton University, New Jersey, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - 193 - Near Eastern Studies, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 181)
  - 194 - Common Council for American Unity, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 182)
  - 195 - Ford Foundation Library, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 183)
  - 196 - Joint Council on Economic Education, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 184)
  - 197 - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (TIAA), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 185)
  - 198 - American Music Center: Boston University, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 186)
  - 199 - Released Faculty Time for ETV - Harvard, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 187)
  - 200 - Massachusetts Institute of Tehcnology, School of Industrial Management, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 188)
  - 201 - Economics and Business Administration Fellowship Program, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 189)
  - 202 - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 190)
  - 203 - Coro Foundation: San Francisco, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 191)
  - 204 - National Academy of Sciences, International Geophysical Year, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 192)
    Photographer: Various
  - 205 - Educational Resources Project (File Missing), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 193)
  - 206 - Council on Library Resources (CLR), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 194)
  - 207 - Council on Library Resources (CLR), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 195)
  - 208 - Piedmont Crescent Region, North Carolina, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 196)
  - 209 - ETV Workshop: Chapel Hill, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 197)
  - 210 - Minneapolis School of Art, Conference on Visual Perception and the Creative Process, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 198)
  - 211 - Dunwoodie Institute, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 199)
  - 212 - Economic Workshop: University of Minnesota, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 200)
  - 213 - Juvenile Officers Institute: University of Minnesota, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 201)
  - 214 - Bulllock-Generated Electrical Power Experiment, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 202)
  - 215 - Little House: Menlo Park, California, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 203)
  - 216 - Indonesian Exchange Program: University of California, Berkeley, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 204)
  - 217 - New England Opera Theatre Co., 1958 (Box 15, Folder 205)
  - 218 - Russian Exchange Students In New York, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 206)
  - 219 - American Federation of Arts, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 207)
  - 220 - University of Illinois, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 208)
  - 221 - Population Reference Bureau, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 209)
  - 222 - Brookings Institution, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 210)
  - 223 - New Orleans Jazz Archives: Tulane University, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 211)
  - 224 - Experiment in Elementary Education, Ossining, New York and Long Beach, New York., 1959 (Box 15, Folder 212)
  - 225 - Hamilton College, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 213)
  - 226 - University Presses, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 214)
  - 227 - National Committee on the Aging, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 215)
  - 228 - Miami University - Ohio, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 216)
  - 229 - English Language Institute, University of Michigan, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 217)
  - 230 - Northwestern University, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 218)
  - 231 - Dillard University, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 219)
  - 232 - University of Alabama, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 220)
  - 233 - Southern Education Reporting Service, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 221)
  - 234 - George Peabody College for Teachers, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 222)
  - 235 - National Program in the Use of Television, Jefferson County, Kentucky, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 223)
  - 236 - Austin College: Sherman, Texas, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 224)
  - 237 - Claremont College, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 225)
  - 238 - John Hay Fellows, Columbia University, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 226)
  - 239 - John Hay Fellows - Nebraska, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 227)
  - 240 - Kansas City Metropolitan Area, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 228)
  - 241 - Institute of Education, University College of Ghana, Achimota, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 229)
    Photographer: Almasy, Paul
    Ghana
  - 242 - Institute of Education, University College, Ibadan, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 230)
    Photographer: Wellwood, A.
    Nigeria
  - 243 - Graduate Institute of International Studies, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 231)
    Photographer: Gooen, I.
  - 244 - Polish Exchange Program: University of Geneva, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 232)
  - 245 - Columbia Law School, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 233)
  - 246 - Southern Methodist Law School, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 234)
  - 247 - University of Kansas Summer Institute on Asia, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 235)
  - 248 - Michigan Law School, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 236)
  - 249 - University of Michigan Summer Institute in Practical Partisan Politics, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 237)
  - 250 - Frank Scangarella: Law Student, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 238)
  - 251 - Harvard Law School: Kingman Brewster, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 239)
  - 252 - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1959 (Box 17, Folder 240)
  - 253 - Columbia University, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 241)
  - 254 - Miscellaneous Scenes of New York City, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 242)
  - 255 - Yale University: Master of Arts Teaching Program, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 243)
  - 256 - University of California, Berkeley, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 244)
  - 257 - National Music Council: Fellowship Program for Young Composers, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 245)
  - 258 - University of California, Berkeley, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 246)
  - 259 - Western Data Processing Center: University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), 1959 (Box 17, Folder 247)
  - 260 - Youth Studies Center: Uuniversity of Southern California (USC), 1959 (Box 17, Folder 248)
  - 261 - Foreign Area Training Fellowship Program, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 249)
  - 262 - Royal Hellenic Research Foundation, Saloniki, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 250)
    Greece
  - 263 - Athens Technological Organization, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 251)
  - 264 - Pakistan Government: Training in Town Planning, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 252)
  - 265 - Franklin School: Lexington, Mass., 1959 (Box 18, Folder 253)
  - 266 - Newton High School: Newton, Mass.: Teacher Utilization, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 254)
  - 267 - Wayland High School: Wayland, Mass.: Teacher Utilization, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 255)
  - 268 - NET: "Hats in the Ring", 1960 (Box 18, Folder 256)
  - 269 - National Educational Television and Radio Center, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 257)
  - 270 - University of Michigan: Engineering Program, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 258)
  - 271 - WCET, Cincinnati Educational Television, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 259)
  - 272 - WMUB, Miami University, Oxford, Ohio Educational Television, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 260)
  - 273 - Newton High School, Newton, Mass: teacher utilization, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 261)
  - 274 - Evanston Township High School, Evanston, Ill. Teacher utilization, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 262)
  - 275 - University of Cincinnati: cooperative industry: university program of engineering education, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 263)
  - 276 - Oberlin College self-teaching machines, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 264)